1forexrebates.com 2014-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Best Forex Rebates Site | 1ForexRebates.com

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, bank details, Moneybookers account details, Paypal account details, Perfectmoney Webmoney account details, information of Forex product purchases through 1ForexRebates.com website, your trading account details at currency exchage brokers. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you);

To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**DO WE USE COOKIES?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information).

We use cookies to help us understand and save your preferences for future visits and keep track of advertisements.

**DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**GOOGLE, AS A THIRS PARTY VENDOR, USE COOKIES TO SERVE ADS ON OUR SITE**

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 16 of January, 2014
